When the last thing you expect becomes the only thing you want.
The Idea of You is a romance, drama, comedy film directed by Michael Showalter.
40-year-old single mom Solène begins an unexpected romance with 24-year-old Hayes
Campbell, the lead singer of August Moon, the hottest boy band on the planet.
As they begin a whirlwind romance, it isn't long before Hayes' superstar status poses unavoidable challenges to their
relationship, and Solène soon discovers that life in the glare of his spotlight might be more than she bargained for.
Solène, played by Anne Hathaway.
Hayes, played by Nicholas Galitzine.
Izzy, played by Ella Rubin.
Tracy, played by Annie Mumolo.
Daniel, played by Reid Scott.
Eva, played by Perry Mattfeld.
The Idea of You is a 2024 American romantic comedy drama film directed by Michael Showalter from a
screenplay he co-wrote with Jennifer Westfeldt, based on the novel of the same name by Robinne Lee.
Starring Anne Hathaway and Nicholas Galitzine, it chronicles the love dilemma
between a single mother and the lead singer of a popular boy band.
A film adaptation of the novel was announced in late 2018 by the producers Cathy Schulman and Gabrielle Union; no further
development was made until in mid-2021 with the involvement of Westfeldt, Hathaway, Showalter, and Galitzine being announced.
The film was shot by cinematographer Jim Frohna predominantly
in Georgia, United States, during late 2022.
Peter Teschner edited the film while Siddhartha
Khosla composed the original score.
Savan Kotecha composed and wrote the original songs.
The Idea of You premiered at South by Southwest on March 16, 2024,
and was released on Amazon Prime Video on May 2, 2024.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, age
difference, singer, forty something, single mother.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.